<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts-rsses on Tom Barlow</title>
    <link>http://tombee.co.uk/posts/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts-rsses on Tom Barlow</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://tombee.co.uk/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Update Unavailable with This Apple ID</title>
      <link>http://tombee.co.uk/posts/2014-10-28-update-unavailable-with-this-apple-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tombee.co.uk/posts/2014-10-28-update-unavailable-with-this-apple-id/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So I just got my new Macbook with Mavericks installed, and when updating to Yosemite I came across this issue when attempting to update the iLife and iWork suite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Update Unavailable with This Apple ID
This update is not available for this Apple ID either because
it was bought by a different user or the item was refunded
or cancelled.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went to the website for Apple support, they called back straightaway but then was in the queue for around 5 minutes.  Tried a few things (which I will list below as well), but here&amp;rsquo;s the solution that worked for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Navigate to Applications and move iMovie and iPhoto to the Trash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open App Store and search for iMovie, accept and install this.  If you get an error &amp;ldquo;Update has already been accepted&amp;rdquo; then click on the purchases tab and click on install for the app&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Repeat the above step for iPhoto&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Re-attempt update of the rest of the iWork/iLife suite, if you get issues with updating other apps then try removing them and re-installing from the App Store as per steps 2 and 3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If that doesn&amp;rsquo;t work, here are a few options that were attempted prior to the solution that worked for me:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created a new user called test, signed in with the same Apple ID and tried again, no luck&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Moved /Library/Preferences/com.apple.storageagent.plist to Desktop temporarily and then re-ran update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Moved to desktop the following files/directories and re-ran update:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;/Users/myusername/Library/Preferences/com.apple.appstore.plist&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;/Users/myusername/Library/Containers/com.apple.appstore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;/Users/myusername/Library/Containers/com.apple.appstore.PluginXPCService&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When in App Store, select Store from the menu bar at the top of the screen, and select sign out.  Sign back in and re-attempt the update.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>